/*
<p> Once upon a time, there was a little girl who lived near the forest.</p>
<p>曾几何时，有一个小女孩住在森林附近的一个村庄里。</p>
<p>Whenever she went out, the little girl wore a red riding <button class="button button1" onclick="alert('an outdoor overgarment,typically sleeveless, that hangs loosely from the shoulders.')">cloak </button>, so everyone in the village called her Little Red Riding Hood.</p>
<p>每当她外出时，这个小女孩都穿着红色斗篷，所以村里的每个人都叫她小红帽。</p>
<p>One morning, Little Red Riding Hood asked her mother if she could go to visit her grandmother as it had been awhile since they'd seen each other.</p>
<p>一天早上，小红帽问她的母亲是否可以去看望她的祖母，因为他们已经见过彼此了</p>
<p>"That's a good idea," her mother said.  So they packed a nice basket for Little Red Riding Hood to take to her grandmother.</p>
<p>“这是一个好主意，”她的母亲说。因此，他们为小红帽收拾了一个漂亮的篮子，带给她的祖母.</p>
<p>When the basket was ready, the little girl put on her red <button class="button button1" onclick="alert('an outdoor overgarment, typically sleeveless, that hangs loosely from the shoulders.')">cloak </button> and kissed her mother goodbye.</p>
<p>当篮子准备好了，小女孩穿上红色斗篷，吻了妈妈再见。
<p>Remember, go straight to Grandma's house," her mother <button class="button button1" onclick="alert('say something as a warning.')">cautioned </button>"Don't<button class="button button1" onclick="alert('move slowly and idly.')">dawdle </button> along the way and please don't talk to <button class="button button1" onclick="alert('a person who does not know, or is not known in, a particular place or community.')">strangers</button> The woods are dangerous."</p><p>“请记住，直接去奶奶家，”她的母亲警告说。 “不要一路骚扰，请不要和陌生人说话！树林很危险。”</p>
<p>"Don't worry, mommy," said Little Red Riding Hood, "I'll be careful."</p>
<p>“别担心，妈妈，”小红帽说，“我会小心的。”</p>
<p>But when Little Red Riding Hood noticed some lovely flowers in the woods, she forgot her promise to her mother.</p>
<p>但是当小红帽在树林里发现一些可爱的花朵时，她忘记了对母亲的承诺
<p>She picked a few, watched the butterflies <button class="button button1" onclick="alert('move swiftly and lightly.')">flit</button> about for a while, listened to the frogs <button class="button button1" onclick="alert('make a characteristic deep hoarse sound.')">croaking</button> and then picked a few more.</p>
<p>她挑了几个，看着蝴蝶掠过一会儿，听着青蛙呱呱叫，然后又挑了几个。</p>
<p>Little Red Riding Hood was enjoying the warm summer day so much, that she didn't notice a dark shadow make <button class="button button1" onclick="alert('come near or nearer to someone or something in distance.')">approaching</button> out of the forest behind her...</p>
<p>小红帽非常享受这个温暖的夏日，她没有注意到她背后的森林里出现了一个黑暗的阴影......</P>
<p>Suddenly, the wolf appeared beside her.</p>
<p>突然，狼出现在她旁边。</p>
<p>"What are you doing out here, little girl?" the wolf asked in a voice as friendly as he could <button class="button button1" onclick="alert('collect or assemble.')">muster </button></P>
<p>“你在这做什么，小女孩？”狼在声音中尽可能友善地问道</p>
<p>"I'm on my way to see my Grandma who lives through the forest, near the brook,"  Little Red Riding Hood replied.</p>
<p>“我正在路上看到我的奶奶住在森林附近的小溪边，”小红帽回答道。</p>
<p>Then she realized how late she was and quickly excused herself, rushing down the path to her Grandma's house. </p>
<p>然后，她意识到自己已经有多晚了，并迅速原谅自己，冲向奶奶家的路</p>
<p>the wolf, in the meantime, took a shortcut...</p>
<p>在此期间，狼走了一条捷径......</p>
<p>The wolf, a little out of breath from running, arrived at Grandma's and knocked lightly at the door.</p>
<p>狼跑了一小口气，来到了奶奶家，轻轻敲了敲门。</p>
<p>"Oh thank goodness dear!  Come in, come in!  I was worried sick that something had happened to you in the forest," said Grandma thinking that the knock was her granddaughter.</p>
<p>“哦，谢天谢地，亲爱的！进来吧！进来！我担心森林里发生了什么事让你感到恶心，”奶奶说，敲门声是她的孙女。</p>
<p>The wolf let himself in.  Poor Granny did not have time to say another word, before the wolf <button class="button button1" onclick="alert('eat something hurriedly and noisily.')">gobbled</button> her up!</p>
<p>狼让自己进去。可怜的奶奶没有时间再说一句话，在狼狼吞虎咽之前！</p>
<p>The wolf let out a satisfied burp, and then poked through Granny's wardrobe to find a nightgown that he liked.</p>
<p>狼出了一个满意的打嗝，然后穿过格兰尼的衣橱，找到了他喜欢的睡衣。</p>
<p>He added a button class="button button1" onclick="alert('decorated with frills or similar ornamentation.')">frilly</button> sleeping cap, and for good measure, <button class="button button1" onclick="alert('press against something lightly with a piece of absorbent material in order to clean or dry it.')">dabbed</button> some of Granny's perfume behind his pointy ears.</p>
<p>他添加了一个褶边睡帽，并且很好的措施，在他尖尖的耳朵后面抹了一些奶奶的香水</p>
<p>A few minutes later,little Red Riding Hood knocked on the door.</p>
<p>几分钟后，小红骑敲门。</p>
<p>The wolf jumped into bed and pulled the covers over his nose.  "Who is it?" he called in a cackly voice.</p>
<p>狼跳到床上，把盖子拉过鼻子。 “是谁呀？”他用一种嘶哑的声音喊道</p>
<p>"It's me, Little Red Riding Hood."</p>
<p>“这是我，小红帽。”</p>
<p>"Oh how lovely!  Do come in, my dear," <button class="button button1" onclick="alert('make a characteristic deep hoarse sound.')">croaked</button> the wolf.</p>
<p>“哦，多可爱！亲爱的，进来吧，”狼嘶哑地说道。</p>
<p>When Little Red Riding Hood entered the little cottage, she could scarcely recognize her Grandmother.</p>
<p>当小红帽进入小屋时，她几乎无法认出她的祖母。</P>
<p>"Grandmother!  Your voice sounds so odd.  Is something the matter?" she asked.</p>
<p>“祖母！你的声音听起来很奇怪。有什么事吗？”她问。</p>
<p>"Oh, I just have touch of a cold," squeaked the wolf adding a cough at the end to prove the point.</p>
<p>“哦，我只是感冒了一下，”狼吵醒了最后加咳，以证明这一点。</p>
